hotelsbycity.com 2017-11-08

# Our Privacy Policy - HotelsByCity.com

Introduction

Priceline Partner Network is owned and operated by priceline.com LLC (together with its subsidiaries, "priceline.com") and is part of The Priceline Group Inc. The following describes the privacy policy (as amended or otherwise changed from time to time, the "Privacy Policy") applicable to the services available through the Priceline Partner Network web site, the Priceline Partner Network mobile site, our iPhone, Android and other mobile applications and any other online communications and interfaces (the "Site") from or provided by Priceline Partner Network. By visiting the Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure, storage, transfer and processing of your personal data described in this Privacy Policy.

On occasion Priceline Partner Network may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our Personal Data collection and use practices, the features of our Site, or advances in technology. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a prominent notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.

Summary of this Privacy Policy

EU Data Transfers | While the European Court of Justice has held that the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework is no longer "adequate" for the transfer of personal data from the EU to the U.S., Priceline.com and its parent company, The Priceline Group Inc., comply with the US/EU and US/Swiss Safe Harbor frameworks for European Customer Data, European Affiliate Data, and European Employee Data.  
---|---  
Information We Collect | We collect Personal Data about you that you provide to us while using the Site.  
How We Protect Your Data | We employ reasonable and current technical, administrative and physical safeguards that are designed to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and designed to ensure correct use of Personal Data.  
How We Use Your Data | We use Personal Data to provide you with the products and services from our Site, to build features that will make the services available on the Site easier to use, to contact you about these services, and to occasionally send advertisements, marketing material or other offers that we think might be of interest to you.  
How We Share Your Data | We share your Personal Data with external service providers (e.g., hotels, airlines, car rental agencies), Priceline Group companies, our third party partners, our agents, and otherwise for compliance with law and other disclosures. In addition, we may also share your Personal Data in the context of any future business transfers.  
Cookies | Our Site uses cookies and other similar technologies. Our mobile websites and mobile apps may use Anonymous Device IDs and/or Advertiser Identifiers in a manner similar to our use of cookies on our websites. To opt-out of advertising and certain other cookies, please see the opt-out links below.  
Accessing or Changing Your Data | Priceline.com understands that you may want to change, access or delete your Personal Data. You may do so by accessing your profile or by contacting us here.  
Children | Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use any services on our Site.  
Contact Us | Should you have any questions, concerns or comments, please click here. Priceline.com LLC is located at 800 Connecticut Avenue, Norwalk, Connecticut 06854.  
  
Our Commitment to Your Privacy

While the European Court of Justice has held that the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework is no longer "adequate" for the transfer of personal data from the EU to the U.S., Priceline Partner Network LLC and its parent company, The Priceline Group Inc. ("Priceline Safe Harbor Entities") comply with the US/EU and US/Swiss Safe Harbor framework ("Safe Harbor") as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union ("EU") and Switzerland. The Priceline Safe Harbor Entities have certified that they adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. In particular, the Priceline Safe Harbor Entities adhere to the Safe Harbor with respect to personally identifiable data obtained in the US about: (i) customers and visitors to this Site from the EU and Switzerland ("European Customer Data"); (ii) suppliers, business partners, customers, and website visitors of our EU and Swiss affiliates ("European Affiliate Data"); and (iii) employees of our EU and Swiss affiliates ("European Employee Data"). EU European Customer Data is handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and any questions about such data should be directed to us as specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view the Priceline Safe Harbor Entities’ certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

We process European Affiliate Data on behalf of, and in accordance with the instructions of, our relevant affiliates in the EU and Switzerland, such as in connection with customer support and other business functions. In addition, in limited circumstances, we may also obtain European Affiliate Data as necessary or appropriate in connection with litigation, government inquiries, internal inquiries, or similar matters. Questions about European Affiliate Data should be directed to us as specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. In addition, we maintain internal policies and procedures governing the handling of European Employee Data. If we or our EU and Swiss affiliates cannot answer or resolve questions about European Employee Data directly, the individual concerned may contact the data protection authorities in their home country in the EU or Switzerland for further information.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. – based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to your friends and family.

Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information ("Personal Data") about you that you provide to us while using the Site. Personal Data includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, credit card number, e-mail address, age, date of birth, gender, username and password for our Site and any other information you may choose to provide or as may be required to fulfill the requested service. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, including your IP address, search preferences related to specific searches, location, and bids through your interactions with our Site. When we link non-personally identifiable information with Personal Data, we will treat at as Personal Data under this Privacy Policy.

Our Site includes links to other web sites and online services whose privacy practices may differ from those of Priceline Partner Network. For example, you can log in to our Site using single sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your network. If you submit personal information to or through any of those web sites or services, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit or online services you use.

The site also includes Social Media Features and Widgets, such as Facebook, Google Plus, Twitter, and YouTube. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

If you purchase certain services, such as airline tickets, for other travelers, we will collect Personal Data of the other travelers that (i) is required to fulfill the requested service and (ii) you may otherwise provide to us. You must make sure that you have the right to provide such information. By providing any Personal Data of another traveler, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such person to enable us to collect, use and disclose such Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Personal Data of other travelers is collected only for the purpose of providing such Personal Data to the appropriate travel supplier, such as the airline on which travel will occur, to fulfill the requested service, or as otherwise may be required by applicable law.

Protecting Your Personal Data

We employ reasonable and current technical, administrative and physical safeguards that are designed to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and designed to ensure correct use of Personal Data. To provide protection for credit card transactions while in transit, Priceline Partner Network currently uses Secure Socket Layer encryption.

How We Use the Information We Collect

We use Personal Data to provide you with the products and services from our Site, to build features that will make the services available on the Site easier to use, and to contact you about these services. This includes faster purchase requests, better customer support and timely notice of new services and special offers and more relevant content.

From time to time, Priceline Partner Network may contact you to request feedback on your experience using the Site, to assist us in improving the Site, or to offer special savings or promotions, marketing material or other offers to you, as a Site user. If you would prefer not to receive notices of special savings or promotions, you may simply opt-out from receiving them by using the hyperlink provided in these notices.

Sharing Your Personal Data

Priceline Partner Network does not share your Personal Data, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise authorized by you. Priceline Partner Network may share your Personal Data with its subsidiaries and with third parties as described in the categories below:

**External Service Providers:** When you use the Priceline Partner Network service to purchase an airline ticket, reserve a hotel room or a rental car or to take advantage of any of our other products and services (including travel insurance and destination attractions), we may provide Personal Data to the airline, hotel, car rental agency or other involved third-party, including other Priceline Group companies, such as priceline.com’s subsidiaries, its parent company or its sister companies including Booking.com BV ("Booking.com"), Agoda Company Pte. Ltd. ("Agoda"), Traveljigsaw Limited ("rentalcars.com"), KAYAK Software Corporation and OpenTable, Inc. Please refer to the websites of third party suppliers for their Privacy Policies and other information on the suppliers.

**Priceline Partner Network's Third Party Partners:** In order to provide you with certain services, we may share your Personal Data with third party partners, or require that you transact directly with a third party partner. Third party partners consist of companies with which Priceline Partner Network has contracted in order to provide you with services or products featured on our Site, such as:

  * _Priceline Cruises._ Priceline Cruises are offered through World Travel Holdings, Inc. ("WTH"). When you provide Personal Data in connection with the purchase or booking of a cruise, you are providing such Personal Data to WTH, which holds such Personal Data on our behalf. Our contract with WTH requires WTH to maintain such Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * _Priceline Group Hotels._ Priceline Group Hotels are offered through Lexyl Travel Technologies, Inc. ("Lexyl"). When you provide Personal Data in connection with the Group Hotels service, you are providing such Personal Data to Lexyl, which holds such Personal Data on our behalf. Our contract with Lexyl requires Lexyl to maintain such Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Please refer to the websites of third party suppliers for their Privacy Policies and other information on the suppliers. We may revise this list from time to time if we decide to offer additional services through these or other third-party partners.

**Priceline Partner Netwroks's Agents:** Many of the operations we perform require us to hire other companies to help us with these tasks. For example, Priceline Partner Network hires companies to help us handle mail and e-mail (including sending and delivering packages, postal mail and e-mail), analyze the data we collect, market our products and services, handle credit card transactions and provide customer service. The companies we employ to help us with these tasks have access to Personal Data to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Priceline Partner Network requires all agents to whom Personal Data is disclosed to enter into confidentiality agreements and to agree to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Policy.

In some instances we utilize service provider platforms to help us provide certain services to you such as our Career services provider where this Policy governs the collection and use of your Personal Data even though you are on a third party website. In these instances you will always know whose privacy policy governs the collection and use of your Personal Data by clicking on the Privacy Policy link provided.

**Future Business Transfers:** Our business is constantly changing. As part of that process, Priceline Partner Network may sell or buy other companies, and Personal Data may be transferred as part of these transactions. It is also possible that Priceline Partner Network, or substantially all of its assets, may be acquired by another company, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, and Personal Data may be transferred as part of such a transaction. In such cases, the acquiring company would be required to honor the privacy promises in this Privacy Policy or obtain your consent to any material changes to how your Personal Data will be handled.

**Compliance with Law and Other Disclosures:** Priceline Partner Network reserves the right to release Personal Data in order to comply with applicable law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us. We may also release Personal Data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions applicable to our products and services, protect us or others against fraudulent or inappropriate activities, or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of Priceline Partner Network, our affiliated companies, our customers, or others.

Our Policy Concerning Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Cookies and similar tracking technologies, such as beacons, scripts, and tags, are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive or device, which enable a website to "personalize" itself for each user by remembering information about the user's visit to the website.

As described in more detail below, our Site uses cookies to store your preferences, display content based upon what you view on our Site to personalize your visit, analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site, serve targeted advertising and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. On mobile websites and mobile apps, we may use Anonymous Device IDs and/or Advertiser Identifiers in a manner similar to our use of cookies on our websites. To opt-out of advertising and certain other cookies, please see the opt-out links below.

**Priceline Cookies (First Party Cookies):** We, at Priceline Partner Network, use our cookies to improve your web-browsing experience. For example, we use a cookie to reduce the time it takes for you to submit purchase requests by storing a registered user's e-mail address so that the user does not need to enter their e-mail address each time that they log-in to Priceline Partner Network. We will also use a cookie to keep track of your search criteria while you are engaging Priceline Partner Network's services. Priceline Partner Network cookies are associated with a user's Personal Data. However, no third party may use the information we collect through our Priceline Partner Network cookies for their own purposes.

**Third Party Cookies:** We work with third-parties that place cookies on our Site to provide their services, including:

      * _**Ad Targeting:**_ We work with third-party advertising companies to serve ads while you are visiting our Site and permit these companies to place and access their own cookies on your computer in the course of serving advertisements on this Site. These companies may use information obtained through their cookie (which does not include your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other websites, in combination with non-personally identifiable information about your purchases and interests from other online sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not ours. Data Providers: We also allow data providers to collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), when you visit our Site, or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with data providers solely in hashed, non-human readable form.
      * _**Analytics/Measurement:**_ We also use third-party analytics cookies to gain insight into how our visitors use the Site, to find out what works and what doesn't, to optimize and improve our websites and to ensure we continue to be interesting and relevant. The data we gather includes which web pages you have viewed, which referring/exit pages you have entered and left from, which platform type you have used, date and time stamp information and details such as the number of clicks you make on a given page, your mouse movements and scrolling activity, the search words you use and the text you type while using our Site. We also make use of analytics cookies as part of our online advertising campaigns to learn how users interact with our website after they have been shown an online advertisement, which may include advertisements on third-party websites.
      * _**Remarketing Pixel Tags:**_ In addition, we may share web site usage information about visitors to our Sites with third-party advertising companies for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our Site and other sites. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising companies may place pixel tags (also called clear gifs) on some of the pages you visit on our Site. We will then use the non-personally identifiable information that is collected using these pixel tags to serve you relevant advertisements when you are visiting other sites on the Internet. These advertisements may be targeted to specific searches you conducted on Priceline Partner Network during earlier browsing sessions.
      * _**Flash Cookies:**_ Our partners, who provide certain features on our site or display advertising based on your browsing activity, also use Local Shared Objects such as Flash cookies, and Local Storage such as HTML5, to collect and store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 local storage. To manage Flash cookies, please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

**Opting Out of Cookies:** We provide you with choice over the use of cookies as described in this Privacy Policy. However, our Site is not currently configured to respond to Do Not Track signals. If you'd rather we didn't use Priceline Partner Network cookies when you visit us, [click here](http://www.priceline.com/static-pages/privacy-policy.html) for how to configure your browser settings to reject cookies.

If you would like to opt-out of third-party cookies, here are some options:

      * \- If you would like to opt-out of ad targeting cookies set by Google and Doubleclick on our Site, please click here: <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en>.
      * \- If you would like to disable the display of advertisements served by Criteo, please click here: <http://www.criteo.com/privacy/full-privacy-text/>.
      * \- If you would like to generally (i.e. not just for this Site) opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website or [click here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). If you are located in the European Union, please [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) to opt out.
      * \- In order to control the collection of data for analytical purposes by Google Analytics, you may want to visit the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.
      * \- If you wish to block other cookies, including those being served by companies that are not part of the NAI or DAA, [click here](http://www.priceline.com/static-pages/privacy-policy.html) for how to configure your browser settings to reject cookies. You can also delete all cookies that are already on your computer's hard drive by searching for and deleting files with "cookie" in it.

**Mobile Devices**

      * \- Anonymous Device Identifiers and Hashed IDs: We and/or data providers that we have engaged may collect and store a unique identifier matched to your mobile device, in order to deliver customized ads or content while you use applications or surf the internet, or to identify you in a unique manner across other devices or browsers. In order to customize these ads or content, we or a data partner may collect de-identified demographic or other data about you received from third parties, as well as data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, and/or data passively collected from you, such as your device identifier or IP address. However, we will share your email address with our data partners solely in hashed, non-human readable form.

If you no longer wish to receive interest-based advertising on your mobile device browser or applications, please refer to your device’s operating system settings, or follow instructions below.

          * \- Android Users (version 2.3 and above): To use the "opt-out of interest-based advertising" option, follow the instructions provided by Google here: [Google Play Help](https://support.google.com/googleplay/answer/3405269).
          * \- iOS users (version 6 and above): To use the "Limit Ad-Tracking" option, follow the instructions provided by Apple here: [Apple Support Center](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074)

Please keep in mind that, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on our Site, including access to your profile/account and certain personalized content. Removing all cookies from your computer could also affect your subsequent visits to certain web sites, including the Priceline Partner Network web site, by requiring that, for example, you enter your login name when you return to that web site.

How You Can Access or Change Your Personal Data

Priceline Partner Network understands that you may want to change, access or delete your Personal Data. You may do so by accessing your profile or by contacting us [here](https://secure.rezserver.com/hotels/help/contact/?refid=1001). To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally-identifying information. Any request to access your Personal Data will be answered in less than 30 days. If you have registered your profile on any of the services available on our Site, your e-mail address and password are required in order to access your profile information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. In addition, we will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

A Special Note About Children

Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use any services on our Site.

How to Contact Us

Should you have any questions, concerns or comments, please [click here](https://secure.rezserver.com/hotels/help/contact/?refid=1001). Priceline Partner Network LLC is located at 3rd Floor 161 Portage Ave East, Winnipeg, MB Canada R3B 2L6.
